5863 NORFOLK CHASE RD PEACHTREE CORNERS, GA (470) 658-5548 wwoods1016@gmail.com

# WILL WOODS

# **ABOUT**

Will Woods is a former musician and educator turned developer. With a wide range of abilities and past experience, Will is the perfect candidate to both work personally with clients and understand the technical side of applications.

Will is frequently involved in volunteer work for the Atlanta Community Food Bank and enjoys cooking, live music, Atlanta sports and spending time at the park with his dog and his wife.

## TECH SKILLS

- → Browser based technologies HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery
- → Server side development APIs, Node.js, Express, ASP.NET
- → Databases MySQL, MongoDB
- → Deployment Git, Heroku

Will's current portfolio of personal projects and applications can be found at wwoods1016.github.io

# SOFT SKILLS

- → Strong written and verbal communication skills
- → Quick, analytical problem solver
- → Well organized and skilled at managing long-term tasks and projects
- → Team player and experienced leader in multiple fields

#### PRIOR EXPERIENCE

## Wheeler High School - Music Educator

2014 - 2018, MARIETTA

- → Hired and managed staff of co-educators.
- → Developed day-to-day practice routines and rehearsal schedules.

#### **Freelance** - Private Tutor, Musician

2011 - 2018, SOUTHEAST US

- → Played professionally in a variety of big bands and jazz ensembles.
- → Taught private lessons for students applying to college programs.

## **EDUCATION**

# Georgia Institute of Technology - Full Stack Web Development

JAN 2019 - JUL 2019, PEACHTREE CORNERS

Currently enrolled in a market-driven professional development program learning front and back end web development.